KEVIN WILDE

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

With over six years commercial experience in Front-End Web Development, I have extensive knowledge of implementing full website builds, responsive sites and web apps. My solid problem solving skills and a keen eye for detail allow me to deliver projects quickly, efficiently and to a high standard.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Freelance Developer, Essence Digital

October 2013 to December 2013

Built the Christmas campaign for eBay.eu, a pinterest style board maker, using backbone.js.

Senior Freelance Developer, Hogarth Worldwide

August 2013

Helped maintain and build Santander pages.

Senior Freelance Developer, Leagas Delaney

March 2013 to July 2013

Helped manage and build the new Leagas Delaney responsive site. Multi region and multilingual, with unique styling and CMS per location. Built an interactive experience for the fall collection for Timberland.

Senior Freelance Developer, Bandstand

December 2012 to February 2013

Worked on multiple small sites for high quality building refurbishments as an extension to the printed brochures.

Senior Freelance Developer, Precedent

Novermber 2012 to December 2012

Managed and built The University of York 50th Anniversary site and GSM London site.

Senior Freelance Developer, Spark44

October 2012

Built an interactive iPad ad for the Jaguar XF Sportbrake ad campaign.

Senior Freelance Developer, Bandstand

September 2012

Built the interactive 'Experience' for 123victoriast.com.

Senior Freelance Developer, Hugo & Cat

May 2012 to August 2012

Prototyping for the new M&G global site. Built the new Hugo & Cat website, using responsive design. Also worked on a project using the backbone.js framework.

Senior Interactive Developer, SapientNitro

September 2011 to May 2012

Working for clients like Vodafone, Unilever and M&S.

To see more of my job history, please visit my LinkedIn profile.

EDUCATION

BA Interaction Design, Ravensbourne College

September 2003 to July 2007

BTEC ND in Multi-Media Design, Southwark College

September 2001 to June 2003

SKILLS

Advanced: HTML (inc. HTML5), CSS (inc. CSS3 animations), Sass, Javascript, jQuery,

AJAX, MODx CMS, Sublime, Photoshop, Email Builds, OSX, Windows.

Intermediate: JSON, XML, SVN, SEO, Git, OOP, Graphic Design, Backbone, Ember

CONTACT

Portfolio: www.kevin-wilde.co.uk

Telephone: +44 (0)7786 084681

Email: mail@kevin-wilde.co.uk

LinkedIn: uk.linkedin.com/in/kwilde